Mira Rayson

OBJECTIVE

I am a career-focused & motivated individual, eager to begin making an impact in the geomatics industry. My goals right now pertain to advancing my experience in the field and to further developing my career specializations.

Some areas of interest include geospatial infrastructure analysis, spatial & location analysis, risk & impact assessment, environmental & sustainability analysis.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

ArcGIS Suite, QGIS
Python, R, JavaScript, HTML &
CSS

Data collection & mining

PostgreSQL database

management

Remote sensing image analytics

Exploratory Data Analysis

Machine & Deep Learning

Geostatistical analytics

Probability Mapping

Spatial decision-making

LOCATION

Halifax, N.S., Canada

PHONE

902.222.3246

EMAIL

mirarayson@outlook.com

EXPERIENCE

JULY 2019 - PRESENT

Server & Bartender - Economy Shoe Shop Bar/Restaurant

MAY 2023 - DEC 2023

Bartender – Finbars Irish Pub

SEPT 2022 - APRIL 2023

Bartender – Primal Kitchen

My years of restaurant experience has enabled me to refine my communicative abilities in pressurized environments. Skills pertaining to effective task management, prioritization, and time utilization have also been keystones of my time in the hospitality industry.

SEPT 2021 - APRIL 2022

Sustainability Consultant - Chicory Blue General Store

Through the Dalhousie Sustainability program, I had the opportunity to help a local business manage their environmental and financial goals. Routing active transportation pathways, assessing renewable energy infrastructure suitability, and cost analysis of energy efficient technology within the business were a few of the most notable responsibilities I had throughout the year.

EDUCATION

Graduate Certificate in Geospatial Data Analytics | NSCC Centre of Geographic Sciences | Set to graduate 2024

- 4.0 GPA
- Set to achieve Honours Distinction for both semesters

Bachelor's Degree in Sustainability | Dalhousie University | Graduated 2022

- 3.5 GPA
- Achieved Principal's List Honor years 2021 & 2022

SUMMARY

My diverse work and life experience have given me a unique perspective on geomatics and its myriad of applications in our evolving world. I have stayed determined and disciplined throughout my education while balancing multiple jobs and maintaining high standards for myself in every area of my life. My passion for geomatics is ever-growing and has its roots in intricate problem solving and analytical abilities. I am beyond excited to enter the industry and begin a long and successful career.

References available upon request.